(Howard:)how do you quantify
the strength of materials?
(Sheldon:)Young's modulus.
(Raj:)Is that right?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Howard:)Okay, how do you prevent
eddy currents in a transformer?
(Sheldon:)Laminate the core material.
(Leonard:)Come on, give
him a hard one.
That was a hard one.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Howard:)How does the flow rate in a pipe
depend on its diameter?
(Howard:)You don't know, do you?
(panting)
(Howard:)What's the matter, smart guy?
(Howard:)Don't know Poiseuille's law?
(coughing)
(gasps)
Thank goodness I got it!
(Sheldon(coughing several times):)Now I can quit
checking my stool.
(Bernadette:)Okay, what are the
potential side effects
(Bernadette:)for our erectile
dysfunction drug?
(Penny:)Headaches, dizziness and nausea.